Finding Aid for CTC Sports visual materials collection, 1988-1997
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
CTC Sports visual materials collection 1988-1997
CTC Sports
0.5 linear feet. (11 items)
97120 Bimu 2
University of Michigan football highlight videos, 1988-1993; videos on career of Bo Schembechler and the Michigan-Ohio State football rivalry, of the University of Michigan basketball team’s second place finish in the NCAA Tournament of 1992 and 1993, and of the University of Michigan 1995/96 NCAA champion hockey team.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Videos were donated by CTC Sports, Inc. through Bob Lipson (Donor No. 8637 ).
No further additions to the records are expected.
The collection is open to research.
CTC Sports of Farmington Hill, Michigan is a video production company that has long worked closely with the University of Michigan Athletic Department. CTC has produced season highlight videos for football since 1988, for the 1992 and 1993 basketball teams and the 1986 NCAA champion hockey team, as well as several special videos on Michigan football. CTC also is producer of the in-season "Michigan Replay" television programs recappping each week's games and featuring the Michigan football and basketball coaches.
The collection includes football season highlight videos 1988-1993, special productions on Bo Schembechler's career and the Michigan - Ohio State football rivalry, the "Fab Five" basketball team's NCAA tournament second place teams of 1992 and 1993 and the 1995/96 NCAA champion hockey team.
Subjects - Visual Materials:
Univeristyof Michigan--Basketball.; Univeristyof Michigan--Football.; Univeristyof Michigan--Hockey.; Schembechler, Bo.
Genre Terms:
Vieotapes.
- Football
  - 1988 "Michigan Replay" (Box 1)
  - 1989 "Bo's Final Season" (Box 1)
  - 1990 "Mo's First Season" (Box 1)
  - 1992 "Go Blue" (Box 1)
  - 1993 "Michigan's Hall of Fame Season" (Box 1)
  - "Woody Versus Bo: The Ten Year War" 1969-1978 (Box 1)
  - "Michigan versus Ohio State: College Football's Greatest Rivalry" (Box 1)
  - "The Schembechler Years: Michigan Replay 1969-1989" (Box 1)
- Basketball
  - 1991-1992 "Shock the World" (Box 1)
  - 1992/93 "Final Four Showdown" (Box 1)
- Hockey
  - 1995/96 "Our Day Has Come" (Box 1)